<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Joseph Scheidt</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Joseph Scheidt</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Joseph Scheidt</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 25 Mar 2018 02:13:50 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Current projects</title>
      <link>/project/my-awesome-project/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Mar 2018 02:13:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/my-awesome-project/</guid>
      <description>What I&amp;rsquo;m working on This blog, mostly! I have quite a few projects completed I&amp;rsquo;d like to share, so I&amp;rsquo;ll be rolling them out now, as I have a little bit of a break from school work. Stay tuned!
What I&amp;rsquo;m learning about I&amp;rsquo;m just finishing up my second term in the Masters in Data Science program at Johns Hopkins, with the courses Data Science and Statistical Methods and Data Analysis.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Number shuffle</title>
      <link>/2018/03/25/2018-03-25-number-shuffle/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/03/25/2018-03-25-number-shuffle/</guid>
      <description>Number Shuffle Fivethirtyeight.com posted a problem in their weekly Riddler article on Friday which I found particularly interesting. It is as follows:
Imagine taking a number and moving its last digit to the front. For example, 1,234 would become 4,123. What is the smallest positive integer such that when you do this, the result is exactly double the original number? (For bonus points, solve this one without a computer.)
After some thought, I was able to reason out how to get to the answer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A new website!</title>
      <link>/2018/03/23/2018-03-23-a-new-website/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/03/23/2018-03-23-a-new-website/</guid>
      <description>Welcome Thanks for visiting! I am very happy to start sharing some of my work in a place where someone besides me can actually see and read about it.
 How I Built This Site Big thanks to the brilliant tutorial written by Emily Zabor.
This site was built using blogdown, and if you are attempting to build a blogdown site you should definitely check out this amazing book.
I am currently using the Ghostwriter Hugo theme, hosted here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/page/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Mar 2018 02:13:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/page/about/</guid>
      <description>About I am a lifelong Seattle-area native with a passion for data science and data analysis. I enjoy reading and exploring how data impacts and can improve the various sectors of our society.
I currently work as an operations manager for a transportation company near Seattle, where I love to find ways to use data to help make better business decisions.
I&amp;rsquo;m working towards a Masters degree in Data Science from Johns Hopkins University.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>/page/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Mar 2018 02:13:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/page/contact/</guid>
      <description>Contact Please feel free to email, LinkedIn message, or tweet at me for any reason using the information linked on the red buttons above. I&amp;rsquo;ll be excited to hear from you! Unless you are a spam bot phishing for my Facebook account login. Then I will be somewhat less excited.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>